Two little mice fell in a bucket of cream.The first mouse quickly gave up and drowned
The second mouse struggled so hard that eventually he churned that cream into butter and crawled out. I was the second mouse. The man who said this was a successful businessman
He's speaking at an elite club in New York that only accepts America's top elite and he's the 58th member
In the audience, his son Frank warmly applauds his father with adoring eyes, but in fact Frank's father is a liar
He can tell a lie like it's the truth. he's always got a way of getting people to trust him. he's got a new rule that the way to get people to respect you have to dress well
With this skill he managed to slip into high society and marry Frank's mother a demure blonde
But it wasn't long before Frank's father tried to keep you out of business. because of tax problems and no major bank would lend to him
The family sold the villa to move into a shabby apartment. Frank transferred to a public school. Frank was mocked by the students as a substitute teacher when he entered the classroom in his uniform, so he pretended to be a teacher. He not only corrected the students who laughed at him, but he was afraid that the substitute teacher would send him away
It took a week for his ploy to be discovered. Instead of scolding him, his father gave his son a bloody look of approval when he returned home yesterday to find a man in his house
Having been under the influence of his father for a long time, Frank seemed to have a preternatural sensitivity to lies. He immediately saw the secret between his mother and a man and a few days later his speculation was confirmed
His parents are in the process of getting a divorce and they're asking him to sign the divorce papers to choose whether to live with his father or his mother and they're trying to keep a cool face
But Frank couldn't take it. He rushed out of his house and ran down the street desperate. He didn't want to go home but he couldn't go anywhere because he had no money
Then he remembered the airdrop check his father gave him and tried to get cash through fraud. He cheated money with the means he learned from his father, but he could not gain others' trust due to his immature technology
He didn't get a penny for Frank's loss. Walking down the street in the middle of the street were a bunch of uniformed pilots and stewardesses
As if inspired, Frank disguised himself as a student journalist and interviewed the pilot, obtained a series of professional information about Van Mae Airlines, and then managed to get a first officer's outfit and credentials. He remembered his father had said that an honest man had nothing to fear
So he tried not to be afraid to walk down the street with his head held high and then he forged a bunch of airline checks on his model plane and cashed them in and people smiled at him all the way
Your level of trust depends on the clothes you wear and your credentials. Then he gets on the plane disguised as an airplane pilot, goes to the pilot yard and brags with the temporary captain. Then he gets a stewardess and catches him the way dad used to do. Then he gets a license and then he uses the bar with the bank teller
After learning about check printing, he went to an auction and bought a check coding machine. In the 1960s, the security system of American banks was not perfect. Frank, who was good at controlling, went on a crime spree and kept a lot of money in his pocket
The mother took it home and the father said with tears in his eyes that the mother was very stubborn and did not want to come back
Fbi agent Carl was in charge of the case and he tracked Frank down to the hotel after he figured out his pattern
Frank doesn't even know he's in trouble and greets his neighbors on the way up the stairs when Carl breaks down the door with a gun
He can't help but walk out of the bathroom with his face poised and his brain racing as he claims to be a Secret Service officer
He ended up with the same suspect who said that Carl was a little late and that he and Patang had apprehended the suspect and then handed Carl his identification wallet
And let Carl see the scene of the escort downstairs that father and son became the props of his lie a lie is more flowing than the truth
Then he picked up Bemagee and the check and said I'm going to get this down and then he walked out and waited for Frank to leave before Carl realized he opened his wallet and found a pile of broken paper
By this time, Frank is already gone. Frank learns that he has made headlines in the newspaper and is called the James Bond of the Air. So he simply orders himself a Bond suit and buys the same sports car and goes on his epic journey in this image
To his surprise, Frank called to ask after him and unapologetically revealed his heart, but Carl did not believe that Carl was aware of Frank's loneliness
He said you just don't have anyone to talk to. Frank hung up the phone with a snap and then Caldron told the waiter
Frank's pseudonyms are all derived from the comic book character's realization that Frank is probably a minor
Since Frank mentioned the New York baseball team on the phone, he targeted young runaways in New York City
And began to gradually investigate the efforts paid off Carl found Frank's mother support Carl finally locked the identity of the suspect
When she learned that her son had faked the missing ticket, her mother rushed to pay him back. Carl told him that Frank had cheated about $1.3 million so far
My mother was stunned while Frank was partying and drinking and having a good time when a friend fell and went to the hospital
Frank rushed to visit a little nurse who was scolded and cried by the doctor. Frank quickly comforted him when he learned in small talk that the nurse with braces was named Brenda. After a soft shower of comfort, the little nurse finally broke his seat and smiled He surrounded Harvard
Wimpy from medical school made it through the interview process and became an emergency room supervisor on the night shift watching surgical videos in his spare time and catching up on medical stuff and Lant was all over the hospital
No one doubted his identity after all, he didn't have to do a lot of things himself. He was more of a face-off for the hospital. Brenda was crazy in love with him and always looked for opportunities to get close to Frank
After hearing that Brenda had been kicked out of the house by her parents because of abortion, Frank fell in love with the girl who had similar experience with him. The two loved her most and completed the sublimation of love. Frank wanted to settle down for the first time
Carl was not idle at this time he was met by Frank's father and learned Frank's address from the letters between him and his son
Maybe the place was long gone by the time Carl and his men arrived in a hurry and Frank was used to firing a bullet and moving the place
His heart was in the air and Carl was taking his time while Frank and Brenda were visiting his future in-laws
At a family dinner, he bragged about passing the bar exam and was about to go back to his old job just in time to run into a gun. My father in law is a veteran prosecutor. What a coincidence to ask again
Frank thought he was clever but in order to make one lie he had to kill more lies. His father in law had seen through his lies. After dinner he called Frank to his room
Frank knew there was no way to hide everything. he said I'm not a pilot or a doctor or a lawyer. I'm just a young man who fell in love with your daughter
The father-in-law did not blame him, but helped him pass the judicial examination in a week. In the evening, the family sat together and played the chorus with joy, warmth and happiness. When Frank saw his parents-in-law dancing together, the scene of deja veja when he saw love and grazing reminded him of his parents
Frank invited his father to his engagement ball and said excitedly that he was now rich enough to buy back all the things he had lost
He persuaded his father to try to win back his mother, but his father went to tell him that his mother had remarried and Frank's heart was heavy. All his efforts were to bring the family closer to Shigehara
But it turned out to be an empty night and he left. Another Christmas Eve Frank called Carl again and this time he asked for peace. He told Carl that he was getting married and wanted to be quiet
Chukal let him go, Carl says that the $4 million debt can't be let go, he must send Frank to prison. After hanging up the phone, Carl sends someone to investigate the mystery of the recent wedding. On the day of engagement, the family and friends gather together, but Carl comes with his team
Radical Frank sensed something was wrong and dragged Brenda into the room while the police were talking to the crowd
He broke out boxes and boxes of money while he excitedly confessed everything to Brenda who had no idea what was going on
I have no idea what he's talking about. It's too urgent to explain. Frank's supposed to meet him at the airport in two days
By the time Carl got there Frank had already jumped and fled leaving Brenda where she was in shock and two days later Brenda showed up as promised
But instead of meeting him, Frank hides in his car and looks around and finds out that the police have already taken care of him
So his heart gave birth to a plan to pick up their forged documents to put on the handsome uniform came to a university to recruit. air hostesses a girl tell their own magic tell their excellent results show talent
Finally, he chose eight girls with long breasts and thighs and pretty faces. Then surrounded by the girls, it seems that the policemen who entered the airport were afraid to see a bunch of air hostesses who appeared out of thin air were already lured away. So Frank sneaked away in the eyes of the police
At this time, Carl received a call from a colleague who said they found someone acting suspiciously. When they got to the front, the other person was just a soldier. There was a driver
Send him in his uniform to pick up a man who is Carl Carl again. Seven months later Carl goes to the experts with the Frank family's goofy-ass new work and learns that the check might have been printed in France
Thinking that Frank's mother was born in France, Carl immediately sets out to find out. But Carl arrives at the printing house. Franco is pushing away the list and printing the lost ticket in a frenzy
He means you stole money from the French. the French already hate you for buying in
There's French cops all over the place and you'll be shot if you run out the door and Frank doesn't believe he's killed too many lies
Can't tell the difference between a lie and a truth. Carl, are you telling the truth? Carl nods firmly. Frank finally relents. He is handcuffed and led away by the French police
Carr promised to extradite him to the United States and after four years of relentless efforts he finally made good on his promise
As the plane was about to land Frank asked to call his father, but Carl told Frank that one of his fathers had died unexpectedly
Frank couldn't take it and locked himself in the bathroom until Carl sensed something was wrong and smashed the door only to find that Frank had disappeared
On closer inspection, he saw that he had removed the handwashing table and got out. At the moment of landing, Frank climbed onto the landing gear and jumped out of the plane. He went to his mother's new house and saw a lovely little girl through the window
The little girl was born by Frank's mother after their marriage. Looking at the happy family together, Frank's eyes welled up with tears. The police came immediately
He raised his hand slowly for the first time without a fight. While Frank was serving a 12-year sentence, Carl stumbled upon Frank's amazing administrative abilities
Frank was officially recruited as an FBI agent with approval but he had to work under Carl's supervision and under control
A few days after he went to work, he was restless again. He put on the captain's uniform and ran away again. Maybe he was used to seeing the sea as his home
Sometimes it's easier to live a lie and I'm going to let you go tonight because I know you'll be back on Monday and there's no one behind you anymore. And on Monday morning he waited and waited and waited for Frank
Tollefrank married and had children and lived a quiet and happy life. He helped the police to solve a number of bank fraud cases and participated in the design of a variety of encrypted checks. He became a well-known expert in the industry and got high salaries from banks and major companies
The game of Cat and Mouse is also a 2002 Steven Spielberg film based on real time
The original was Frank Abanel, the youngest international wanted man in the history of the fbi who was described by some as the greatest fraud artist of the 20th century according to historical records he impersonated no fewer than eight identities pilot teacher doctor warning lawyer and so on
He escaped from prison twice and all of this happened before he was 21 and Heira's life was a lonely one because you couldn't say the truth to anyone and this is the monologue that Abanel had when he was a child
He was acutely aware that there was a price to be paid for telling the truth and he knew that if it wasn't for the uniform and the badge
People don't think highly of you and you get hurt when you tell the truth and you get trust when you lie. Whether the world teaches children to speak or whether children are born to speak
When Frank wants to leave again, Carl says that there is no one after you anymore. In the movie, his father always teaches Frank to keep messing with your life like a second mouse
But the rebellious nonsense in his youth was. because he knew there were a pair of eyes behind him. When the eyes were not his nonsense, his torment and who to see. He grew up, he was tired of torment
Perhaps the greatest sadness for young Frank is that. he had a place to learn all the professional knowledge. but no place to learn how to be a human being